{
    "subject": "Margaret_of_Anjou",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Henry_VI_of_England",
    "human_readable": "Margaret of Anjou is married to Henry VI of England.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9178377985954285,
            "question": "To whom was Margaret of Anjou married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8784360289573669,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Margaret of Anjou and Henry VI?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551375865936279,
            "question": "What is the name of the English monarch who was married to Margaret of Anjou?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8551375865936279,
            "question": "What is the name of the English monarch who was married to Margaret of Anjou?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7603829503059387,
            "question": "Was Margaret of Anjou married to a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7117424607276917,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Henry VI?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6523728966712952,
            "question": "Was Margaret of Anjou the wife of a powerful ruler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34872639179229736,
            "question": "Who was the queen consort of England during Henry VI's reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30292630195617676,
            "question": "Identify the queen consort of England during the time period of Henry VI."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27035361528396606,
            "question": "Who held the position of queen consort during Henry VI's reign?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Margaret of Anjou is married to Henry VI of England.",
            "html": "yago_27876_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Identify the queen consort of England during the time period of Henry VI.",
            "html": "yago_27876_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the queen consort of England during Henry VI's reign?",
            "html": "yago_27876_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Margaret of Anjou the wife of a powerful ruler?",
            "html": "yago_27876_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27876_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is \"Margaret of Anjou is married to Henry VI of England.\" The documents contain the following information:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27876/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt, it is mentioned that Margaret of Anjou was \"the wife of Henry VI of England\".\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27876/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt, it is mentioned that Margaret of Anjou was the Queen consort of England by marriage to King Henry VI.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27876/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt, it is mentioned that Margaret of Anjou was Queen of England by marriage to King Henry VI from 1445 to 1461 and again from 1470 to 1471.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_27876/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt, it is mentioned that Margaret of Anjou was the Queen Consort of Henry VI.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently provide information that supports the statement \"Margaret of Anjou is married to Henry VI of England,\" mentioning her role as Queen consort multiple times."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}